<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Show Draftees Weapon</name>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <author>targhetti</author>
  <url>https://github.com/duhranged/ShowDrafteesWeapon</url>
  <description>Shows drafted pawn's weapon icon on the colonist bar.

When a pawn has been drafted their equipped weapon icon will display under the pawn's avatar on the colonist banner. New mod settings have been included to allow weapons to be shown regardless of a pawn's drafted status and while they are traveling.

Notes:
- Will work with existing saves
- Can be enabled/disabled without issue

Compatibility:
This mod should be compatible with mods that don't change the Colonist Bar.
That said, it's been designed to be unobtrusive and as such will most likely work with other Colonist Bar mods provided this mod is set to load after the other mod(s). 

The following mods have been tested without issue (screenshots include some of these mods):

- Color Coded Mood Bar - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1501832876
- HandyUI - Fast Colonist Info - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1653465834
- Vanilla Weapons Retextured - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1685182223
- Duel Weld - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1628211313
- Squad UI Tweaks - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1455382219

Latest Updates/Fixes:
- Added two mod settings to control when weapons are shown.
The settings can be accessed via... Options > Mod Settings > Show Draftee's Weapon

Settings:
- Show When Not Drafted - When checked weapons will display regardless of the pawn's drafted status.
- Show When Traveling - When checked weapons will display when pawns are traveling, and their drafted status meets the Show When Not Drafted setting.

Known Issues:
- Beer (beer bottle) and Wood Log items will not display in the colonist bar When equipped as weapons.
</description>
</ModMetaData>