<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>targhetti.ShowDrafteesWeapon</packageId>
  <name>Show Draftees Weapon</name>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <author>targhetti</author>
  <url>https://github.com/duhranged/ShowDrafteesWeapon</url>
  <description>Shows a pawn's weapon icon on the colonist bar.

  - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
** Updated to support Rim World version 1.1 (unstable release) **

The mod now supports versions 1.0 and 1.1.

Version 1.0 should continue to work as it has, without issues.

Version 1.1 as had limited testing and appears to work without issues. That said, Rim World version 1.1 is defined as unstable and there are no guarantees version 1.1 of this mod will work 100% with Rim World or other mods.

Any issues discovered with version 1.1 of this mod will be remedied once Rim World's 1.1 is released as a stable version.

  - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 

When a pawn has been drafted their equipped weapon icon will display under the pawn's avatar on the colonist banner. New mod settings have been added to allow weapons to be shown regardless of a pawn's drafted status and while they are traveling. The settings can be accessed via... Options &gt; Mod Settings &gt; Show Draftee's Weapon.

Settings:
- Show When Not Drafted - When checked weapons display regardless of the pawn's drafted status.
- Show When Traveling - When checked weapons display when pawns are traveling, and their drafted status meets the Show When Not Drafted setting.

Compatibility:
- Will work with existing saves
- Can be enabled/disabled without issue
- This mod should be compatible with mods that don't change the Colonist Bar. That said, it's been designed to be unobtrusive and as such will most likely work with other Colonist Bar mods provided this mod is set to load after the other mod(s).

The following mods have been tested without issue (screenshots include some of these mods):

- Color Coded Mood Bar - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1501832876
- HandyUI - Fast Colonist Info - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1653465834
- Vanilla Weapons Retextured - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1685182223
- Duel Weld - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1628211313
- Squad UI Tweaks - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1455382219
- Pawn Badge - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1696834823

Known Issues:
- Is not compatible with the Colonist Bar KF mod - https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=729908976

Change Log:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/1690978457

GitHub:
https://github.com/duhranged/ShowDrafteesWeapon
  </description>
</ModMetaData>